The main question is…
What factors contribute to the go/no-go decision?
I was going with colour, size…
It's hard to know. There's so much to consider.
In this case, let's see if we can leverage our experience.
Okay, yes, of course.
Perhaps similar projects could tell us something.
Okay — what about last year? The floss project, right?
Same thing. We were trying to decide
whether to enter the market with a new product.
What was the critical data on that project?
I remember hinging the decision
on what our customers were willing to pay for it.
So the price point, right? But is it applicable here?
The competitive landscape for both products is similar.
Why didn't we think of this before?
— Well, we've thought of it now.
And I'm thinking the price points are similar, and the target market.
That is a great comparison across multiple dimensions. Nice work.
Price — not colour or size.
For now, yes. We'll just focus on the important questions.
What are they willing to pay for this product?
That will be the focus of our research.
I'm almost thinking now of the…
— The brightening strip project.
Yes, so similar. And if I recall correctly,
a big piece of the critical data was… anyone?
Performance specifications.
— Performance specifications.
It was before you joined the company.
— Brightening strips, yeah, that's it.
A good example. Anyway, what we found out
was that the decision came down to
what performance specifications had to be equal to
or better than the competitors' products.
So do they make your teeth whiter — or at least as white?
— Yeah.
That was one of the most important ones, in fact.
Let's quickly revise our research budget, assuming
that we're just focusing on these important questions.
See — now we've come down from a 50-lakh proposed budget
to, I guess, 15 lakhs.
That's awesome.
Yeah — by tightly focusing our research on the questions
which have been helpful on similar projects in the past.
What do you think? Are we ready to present?
— Yes.
Let's go! Let's not keep Apoorva waiting. Let's go.
Don't worry — colour and packaging, we'll get you next time.
I think Apoorva was really impressed
by the clarity and focus of the proposal.
And the price tag.
Great job, guys. I'm very excited to find out
what our research tells us.